loadtv.biz 2017-01-21

# Privacy Policy | Download TV Shows and Movies

Please use link **[Keep2Share](http://keep2share.cc/pr/11569)** and **[Publish2.me](http://publish2.me/pr/11569)** and[ **Tezfiles.com**](http://tezfiles.com/pr/34128) to **REGISTER** or **RENEW** your account to support us. We need your support to keep this website alive!

**Both Movies & TV Shows** **TV Shows Only** **Movies Only**

Our website is extremely crucial on the privacy of the information about our users. LoadTV.biz provides information about the TV Shows, actors and actresses. On this site there are no materials that are protected by copyright.

 **Information provided by you:**  
We collect the information you provide at the registration or by any other way (through your messages). Registration forms require user’s name, e-mail address and a password. In addition, after being registered on our website you are obligated to follow the General rules of conduct. We keep the right to take the following actions with the registrational and impersonal information around the world: to use it for our work, to have an access, to process it, to expose, to public, to transfer, to keep, to sell, to investigate, to check and to conduct other operations over the information by our own will or as required by law.

 **Automatic information reception:**  
LoadTV.biz does not use cookies.  
DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on LoadTV.biz.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to LoadTV.biz and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. «Сookie» can get on your computer after clicking at the banner. The website is not responsible for the control of these organizations, their confidentiality provisions or their «cookies».

 **Privacy Policy changes:**  
Please, take into your consideration that the given Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not restrict your rights given by the present Privacy Policy without your valid authorization and believe that similar changes will be minor for the most part. Regardless of the changes’ character, they will be published on this page. If the changes are significant we will provide a more noticeable notification (including, in case of some services, an e-mail notification about the changes in Privacy Policy). Every Privacy Policy version will be marked with an effective date at the bottom of this page.

 **Contact information:**  
If you have any questions about the given Privacy Policy, please, contact us through our website or send an e-mail to: LoadTV.biz@gmail.com.  
In case if we need to contact you we will use the e-mail you voluntarily posted on the website.
